bingohall.ag 2012-06-22

# Contact Online Bingo Hall.com

> Privacy Policy Bingo Hall
> 
> #### General
> 
> Bingo Hall.com ("Bingo Hall", "us" or "we" in this statement) is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. In order to better assist you with the services we provide, certain anonymous information and certain personal information may be collected by us when you visit and/or register at Bingo Hall. The following statement serves to disclose the information gathered by Bingo Hall and how we handle that information to protect your privacy. 
> 
> #### Anonymous Web Site Information
> 
> The Bingo Hall Web site will automatically log IP addresses that access the site. This is part of our Web site's operation and for our own statistical analysis of site traffic. This may also include other information gathered by way of 'cookies' such as pages viewed, the date and time the site was accessed, the type of Internet browser you are using and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our site. However, this anonymous Web site information automatically collected does not personally identify you. 
> 
> #### Advertising
> 
> As is customary in Internet commerce for advertising purposes, the Bingo Hall site system will log IP addresses to supply more accurate advertising features such as language specific banners. The information is used solely for Internet purposes and it is not shared with any third party. Email addresses will only be used to provide our players with a variety of information pertaining to our online bingo promotional Newsletters, software updates and miscellaneous Bingo Hall material. 
> 
> #### Personal Account Information
> 
> You may be required to provide personal information such as your name, address, telephone number and email address in order to register an account at Bingo Hall and make deposits, withdrawals, participate in promotions and receive certain information from us. A wall of security and confidentiality surrounds the personal information you provide. It is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties; furthermore, personal identifiable information of our customers is only accessed by Bingo Hall employees on a restricted "need to know" basis. In order to maintain correct and accurate personal information, you may be able to update your personal details at your sole discretion, not withstanding that you must meet our account security requirements such as providing valid documents to do so. Your winnings and withdrawals are also covered by our privacy policy. At Bingo Hall your winnings and cash-outs are kept strictly confidential in a secure environment and we do not provide this information to any third party unless law, regulation or any governmental or competent regulatory authority requires such disclosure. 
> 
> #### Privacy and Security
> 
> We maintain the utmost means available to keep your information safe with us. All information is transferred using encryption technology and once on our servers it is maintained safe. Both the Bingo Hall Web site and its related software uses the latest technologies to ensure data accuracy and privacy to thus, protect your data from being misused and/or lost.
> 
> #### Changes to Privacy Policy
> 
> We reserve the right, at any time and without prior notice, to add, change, update or modify this statement of the Bingo Hall privacy policy simply by announcing such modifications on our Web site. 
> 
> If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, data security and protection, please do not hesitate to contact Bingo Hall Customer Support.
